

Technically-minded professional with extensive experience troubleshooting and repairing electronic or software related issues. Well-versed in installing computer systems and network topologies. Demonstrated highly developed sense of integrity and commitment to business continuity. Strong commitment to handle multiple simultaneous end user service requests with complete accuracy. Exemplary communication and interpersonal skills; ensure the ability to network skillfully and build mutually beneficial relations. Thrives in challenging, fast-paced, and high-pressure environments by utilizing outstanding problem solving, leadership, and organizational abilities.

Education

B.S. Information Science & Technology

University of Wisconsin, Milwaukee September 2019 — Present

Science Transfer

Portland Community College, Portland March 2016 — December 2016

HS Diploma

Bellevue College, Bellevue July 2000 — March 2002

Professional Trainings

Information Technology Ethics University of Wisconsin, Milwayl

University of Wisconsin - Milwaukee September 2019 — November 2019

Library & Information Science

University of Wisconsin – Milwaukee September 2019 — November 2019

Unix / Linux

Portland Community College July 2016 — September 2016

Computer Science

Portland Community College March 2016 — June 2016

Certifications

Comptia A+

Technical Proficiencies

Platform: Windows (Linux); Android & Apple Mobile Platforms

Tools: Soldiering, Re-flow ovens, Re-ball stations; Networking tools like

putty (connection to non-GUI devices); Wifi Analyzers; Firmware

Flashing Tools; Acronis Software

Hardware: Desktops; Laptops; Networking Hardware; Mobile Devices;

Printers; Smart Devices; Servers, Web Cams; Modern Electronic

Devices

Career Experience

Builders Design inc., Portland Technical Support Specialist

February 2017 — August 2019

Identified and resolved overall technical issues in a timely manner using appropriate course of action. Wholly responsible for keeping company up and running both with hardware and configuration; overcame network connection shortfalls. Held full accountability for troubleshooting peripherals such as printers, mouse, and keyboard.

- Credited for updating and troubleshooting drivers for devices.
- Designed and maintained entire networks.

The Running Box / Cynosure Techworks, Portland March 2009 — February 2017 Electronics Repair Technician

Ensured high success rate at repairing electronics through tactical planning.

• Introduced and rolled-out way to repair an overheating issue with gaming console. Leveraged plasma torch to modify case allowing for more airflow.